JULIETA GARCIA.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PHONE

+54 911 7365 7252 (ARG)

PORFOLIO

juliegarcia.netlify.app

REPO

github.com/Julietteve

LINKEDIN

in/julieta-eva-garcia/

e-MAIL

julieta.eva.garcia@gmail.com

I have always been strongly committed with my career and the resilience it takes to succed.

I am an analytic professional with experience in web and mobile front-end development, focus on excellence and attention to detail. Archiving greatness by working with others and learning by doing.

SKILLS.

LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5 | CSS3 - SASS | REACT NATIVE | REACT JS | ANGULAR JS | JAVASCRIPT ES6 | TYPESCRIPT | MERN STACK

TOOLS

GIT

Console management Code Editors: VC-ST MYSQL Workbench POO Eloquent Responsive design Version control systems NPM - YARN Redux

SOFTWARE

Microsoft Suite Office Adobe package Figma

LANGUAGES PROFICIENCIES

Advanced English Beginner Mandarin Native Spanish

METHODOLOGIES

Scrum Agile methodologies

WORK EXPERIENCE.

2021 - TODAY

Front-End Developer at ABSTI S.A

- Web and Mobile front-end development using React Js and React Native.
- · Prototyping and UI design.
- · Layout design
- Angular JS Apps maintenance

2019 - 2021

Developer at Freelance work w/ temporary clients.

- · Customized Prototyping and UI design.
- Development of fully functional API REST with Node JS and Express.
- · Front-end development with React JS.
- · Development of fully responsive websites.

EDUCATION.

2020 - 2021

National University of Technology (UTN)

Higher Technical in programming.

2013 - 2019

University of Buenos Aires (FADU)

Bachelor's Degree in Multimedia Design.

2011 - 2015

Higher School of English Culture

Foreign Language Professorship.

FURTHER EDUCATION.

2020 - 2021

Acamica

Advanced FrontEnd w/ReactJS.

2020 - 2020

IT Education

Javascript Advanced.

2019 - 2019

Digital House Coding School

Full Stack Development.